RESUME

SANCHEZ

lesliiee727@gmail.com

+19095622938

🏠 Colton, CA 92324

>Presentation Skills

>Detail-Oriented >Microsoft Office

>Google Drive

>Hardworking

>Team Player

>Self-Motivated

>Quick Learner

>Localization

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

Japanese: Elementary

>Bilingual Communication

>Basic Digital Skills (HTML)

>Basic Coding (Javascript)

>Project Management >Team Coordination

>Digital Communication

SKILLS

LESLIE N.

Hardworking and hopeful young adult with extensive education and experience in many

development.

SUMMARY

- Provide fair, friendly, and courteous service for a positive customer experience - Register sales on a cash register while also resolving customer issues and answering clients' auestions. - Maintain checkout operations by following policies and procedures and reporting

levels of bilingual customer service, in a variety of cultures, and of translations and interpretations in educational settings. Ambitiously searching for opportunities to build

my skills and experience toward a career in translation, interpreting, and software

Support Associate, Tory Burch, Ontario, CA 12/2022 - current

WORK HISTORY

>Special Needs Populations >Linguistic Skills (Translation)

>Colombian-Spanish Dialect >Mexican-Spanish Dialect

needed changes. - Assure a safe and clean environment by complying with procedures and regulations.

- Contribute to team effort by accomplishing individual tasks and related results.

Direct Support Staff, Esperanza Services, Alhambra, CA 08/2022 - 10/2022

- Tracked and reported on the company's strategic development and ongoing forecasts. - Update and complete logic documentation for financial and customer data.

- Created and compiled weekly and monthly reports and maintained archival records and database systems. - Worked with accuracy and attention to detail.

- Effectively managed consumers' budgets and reduced spending.

Fulfillment Associate, Macy's Inc, Santa Barbara, CA 10/2020 - 05/2022 - Communicated with floor managers to determine merchandise placement.

- Contact carriers to arrange shipping and delivery of items. - Receive and store shipping goods and supplies.

English: Native Phone Banker, SBX, Riverside, CA

09/2020 - 10/2020

- Contacted consumers via phone or in person to deliver political service information. - Kept records of client interactions including enquirers complaints, and responses.

Volunteer Assistant, Pedley Square Vet Clinic, Riverside, CA 09/2020 - 10/2020 - Stay up to date on advancements in the subject, read recent literature, speak with

coworkers, and furthered my education.

- Collect information and present it, including suggestions for improvement as necessary, on issues like patient interactions and inter-institutional issues.

- Assisted veterinary assistants in general animal healthcare.

Fulfillment Center Associate, Amazon, San Bernardino, CA 07/2019 - 09/2019

- Build, line, and pad boxes, cartons and containers by utilizing tooling.
- Remove completed or faulty goods or materials, placing them on moving equipment such as conveyors or in defined regions such as loading docks.
- Acquire, transport, and sort products, supplies, containers, and orders, utilizing tooling.
- Examine and check containers, materials, and products to ensure that packing criteria are satisfied.

EDUCATION

Rialto High School, Rialto, CA

Graduated 06/2018

GPA: 4.2 Class Rank: Top 10%

Member of: Advancement Via Individual Determination (AVID) - President (2015-2018), Becoming a Mentor (BAM) - Cofounder (2017-2018)

University of California, Santa Barbara (UCSB)

Graduated Fall 2022

Degree: Bachelor of Arts, Spanish

Relevant Coursework: Spanish Language and Law, Intro to Interpretation, USA-Mexico Border Narrative, Mexican Culture, Specialized Legal Translation, Basque Language/Culture, Intro to Translation, Spanish Translation for Healthcare

Member of: Hermanas Unidas (2018-2020), Pre-Veterinary Medical Association (2020-2021)

CERTIFICATION

CPR/AED/First-Aid Certification

CERTIFIED COURSES

Localization Essentials, Udacity 10/2022 Machine Translation, Coursera 10/2022